# JESÚS ANTONIO FERRER SÁNCHEZ

I'm not Junior, Semi Senior, or Senior software developer. Just I'm a simple coder that like Golang and do stuffs on web. Saving experiences in blogs, repos, gists, groups, chat servers, online courses, mind and heart... because the computer can fail and it has happened to me:(



Github: github.com/zeroidentidad
Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/zeroidentidad
Professional license: 10871807

cedula.buholegal.com/10871807

Page: zeroidentidad.github.io Number: +52 9141239545 Location: Tabasco, México

#### FOCUS ON SKILLS:

Golang | JavaScript | PostgreSQL [PgSQL]

#### MAIN PREVIOUS SKILLS:

HTML-CSS | PHP | MySQL | Oracle [PLSQL] | Servers [Windows / Linux] | Docker | JasperReports | VPNs | WordPress | PC maintenance | Android [Java]

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Evening Dresses

June 2021 - Present

**Full Stack Developer:** 

☑ Ember.js web clients development and maintenance

☑ Golang Rest API's development and maintenance

☑ Google Cloud Platform editor

December 2018 - Present

April 2015 - July 2015 (4 months)

# Go / Golang Developer freelance:

A gopher in continuous training. Doing stuffs, mainly about web development.

**♥** Blog: awebytes.wordpress.com

**⊗** Community: gophers-latam.github.io

Contab y Asociados S. C.

*May 2016 - November 2018 (2 years and 7 months)* 

#### **Software Developer:**

☑ Maintenance, updating and development of accounting harmonization systems, payroll and results management.

☑ JSP webapps development (JEE-Oracle 10/11g)

# **Aplicaciones Creativas**

# **Project Collaborator:**

☑ Collaboration in the reporting modules for the one-stop-shop procedure system in public works offices of the central municipality government. - PHP development with Laravel

#### **EDUCATION**

# Universidad Juárez Autónoma de Tabasco

- ✓ University degree: Bachelor of Computer Systems, period August 2010 December 2015
- ✓ Courses: Foreign language English, period August 2010 December 2014

# Universidad de Sonora

- ✓ Courses: 10th Summer of Scientific Research, period June August 2014
- + More EXPERIENCE & EDUCATION data in: linkedin.com/in/zeroidentidad

#### ONLINE TRAINING

- Udemy profile: udemy.com/user/jesus-antonio-ferrer-sanchez [...to see, you need to be a user]
- CódigoFacilito profile: codigofacilito.com/usuarios/zeroidentidad
- Platzi profile: platzi.com/p/zeroidentidad
- Google developer profile: developers.google.com/profile/u/103921680464766832572